"Mob 2
~Rival~"
Wait, was there an accident?
What the heck?
--He's bleeding.
--Whoa, this is bad.
Oh, God...
Uh...
I-I need to call an a-ambulance...
What street is this?
He's not moving...
D-Dude...
Wh-What the...? My phone--
H-Hey, bro?
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
I realized that my youth was grey
The root of this irritation is unknown
My brain runs parallel with this emotional train
Struggling adolescence
Don't disturb the subconscious mind
Who's that behind me?
Opposing ideas, distortion
Purge the sorrow
So, do what you can now.
My life
Finally
Break it down!!
(WANT) desire (YOUNG) and sincerity
(BURN) they begin to sprout (1) within my chest
(TRANCE) I won't awaken (CHANCE) but I want to
(STANCE) both sides of the coin
(1) are back-to-back
Accept me as I am
Conflicting freedom and relations
If they can become one
That smile will be
One and only "1"
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
"Mob Psycho 100 "
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
Come on, Ly-chan. Hurry.
Okay.
Why the hell is there traffic here?
Hey, we're gonna be late.
I know--
Wh-What the--?
An earthquake?
I don't know!
What's happening?
Hey, my phone's not working.
Hey, what the hell is this?!
What's going on?!
--An earthquake?!
--An explosion?!
What the hell?
"Spirits"
Everyone in the area should follow
evacuation orders immediately.
Man, this earthquake sucks.
And it's long, too.
This says there are accidents and
crashes happening everywhere.
The cause is unknown. Most of
the major roads in Seasoning City
"POC@TIN Soldier: Is Earth falling apart? Takoyaki Shut-in: I want takoyaki. I don't care MyWaifuMyWaifu: Isn't that the same place that broccoli
went flying off? MekabuFTW: There's an evacuation order for Seasoning City!" The cause is unknown. Most of the major roads in Seasoning City
"POC@TIN Soldier: Is Earth falling apart? Takoyaki Shut-in: I want takoyaki. I don't care MyWaifuMyWaifu: Isn't
that the same place that broccoli went flying off? MekabuFTW: There's an evacuation order for Seasoning City!"
"POC@TIN Soldier: Is Earth falling apart? Takoyaki Shut-in: I want takoyaki. I don't care MyWaifuMyWaifu: Isn't that the same place that
broccoli went flying off? MekabuFTW: There's an evacuation order for Seasoning City!" are apparently backed up due to restricted access.
Are apparently backed up
due to restricted access.
Oh, looks like an evacuation
order's been issued.
Aw, but Shigeo-kun was
gonna ask that girl out.
Yeah, that's not happening today.
Th-The suspect is around 160 centimeters tall...
Um... and wearing a school uniform
and h-holding a bouquet...
H-He's advancing... as he destroys
buildings around him...
Wh-Why...?
C-Come in!
Thank goodness, I made it in time.
I had a hunch you'd be here,
so I flew over at the speed of light.
Pretty cool, huh?
So you're destroying everything you touch.
I'm not sure what happened,
but if I'd suffice, I'd be happy to lis--
Wait, seriously?!
Come on. Calm down.
Well? I've gotten stronger, too, haven't 1?
I thought I'd try a bit harder
after observing you.
Oh, you bought flowers! That's great!
But it might be a little dangerous
going as you are right now.
I'm not getting through to him?
You leave me no choice.
I'm gonna have to restrain you!
Sorry!
I'm gonna have to keep you restrained
until your powers calm--
Shit!
Ultimate Barrier!
The way you are right now...
...reminds me of when we first met.
Kageyama-kun...
Stop this. You should head home for the day.
It's for your own good.
Kageyama-kun taught me
something very important...
How I was the one who was average
for relying on these powers.
How important it is to accept yourself
without any psychic powers.
I can tell... that Kageyama-kun
is trying to do just that.
Kageyama-kun...
...isn't the kind of person
who'd hurt others!
He reacted!
If I destroy those...
Say, Kageyama-kun...
You're not supposed to use your
psychic powers against others, right?
Something just came flying!
Hey, what the hell was that sound?!
Oh, no...
--Mommy!
--Who the hell is this guy?!
He's destroying things as he walks?!
Get away! He's dangerous!
Another earthquake!
Not here, Kageyama-kun!
There are people who haven't evacuated yet!
Kageyama-kun's powers just keep growing...
What can I do?
Everyone! It's dangerous here!
Please get to shelter immediately!
This is the epicenter of the disaster!
Please just get as far as you can!
Ly-chan!
Kageyama-kun, are you having
some kind of episode?
To think you, of all people,
would go berserk
and lose control of your powers...
I guess you're pretty average, too!
I'm a bit relieved, honestly.
No...
Wait! There are still people here!
Help!
Daddy! Mommy!
--I don't want to die!
--Someone help!
Mommy! Help me!
Someone help!
I know this for sure...
I've been watching this whole time...
You're an absolutely gullible softy...
...but you're still really strong...
And yet, you...
Back then...
...when we first met...
...you were crying by yourself.
I'm sure that's the case even now.
You're crying, aren't you, Kageyama-kun?
Well?!
You want someone to stop you!
Don't you?!
Kageyama-kun!
What...?
What's going on with me?
Hanazawa-kun!
I can tell... that I did this.
I'm the one who did this...
...to Hanazawa-kun, too...
He tried everything he could to stop me
until he ended up like this?
There are times when things
don't work out...
It's fine if people laugh at you.
I'm average, too.
That's enough, Hanazawa-kun...
You don't have to think of this as me.
I can't stop this thing, either.
You can fight back!
Yes! Use your powers against me!
But don't underestimate me!
I'm
I'm your...
I'm your rival!
I guess I win this time!
Seriously, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Get a clue already, Koyama.
The items closer to expiry date
go front and center.
Is it that hard to understand?
If you don't, the old bentos--
All right, jeez!
I'm just trying to get our customers
the best products possible.
Have you ever witnessed the moment
a chicken pasta salad on display three hours ago
gets thrown in the trash?
Nothing in this world is darker than that.
Well, I can't sell old rice balls
to a customer with a smile.
Now, listen here. You need to do
as you're told sometimes.
Did you forget who recommended
you to the manager?
"Koyama"
"Koyama" I'm grateful for what
the manager has done for me.
"Koyama"
And that's exactly why I'm gonna protect...
...our store.
As I figured, all this destruction
was caused by an esper.
And he's headed right for
our convenience store.
Hey... That's that one shitty little brat!
What?!
I see... it all makes sense now.
Hey, you little shit!
I have no idea what's going on,
but I ain't gonna hold back
if you're coming for us!
Tch. He's not stopping.
Very well. Then we're going to have to act.
Telekinetic Helix!
Jugan: Oden Tongs!
"Ramen Egg Prefecture
Experiencing Violent Tremors"
"Ramen Egg Prefecture Experiencing Violent Tremors" --After the incident
at Seasoning Apartments, many other buildings continue to crumble...
"Ramen Egg Prefecture Experiencing Violent Tremors" --That's not good...
--After the incident at Seasoning Apartments, many other buildings continue to crumble...
--That's not good...
I should've asked him for his phone number.
Mob-kun is going to show up, right?
Hey, look at this.
This is a picture of the incident
location posted online...
That's...
Could that be Psycho Helmet-sama?
--It must be!
--Wait, but why?
Captain! Isn't the guy in this picture...
It really isn't dying down.
I guess we better comply with
the evacuation orders, too.
What about Shigeo-kun?
Whoa, there.
I can't get through to him.
I think his phone is off.
But we really don't need
to worry about Mob...
What's wrong?
Reigen-san. Look.
Mob?
Apparently, they've managed to evacuate
everyone including the elderly and children.
We can use as much of
our powers as we'd like.
Electronics aren't working in the area,
and the controls for vehicles, such as
cars and helicopters, stopped working.
So you'll be going down with parachutes.
If you're able to help with the situation,
they'll consider reducing your sentences,
so go do your best out there.
Don't forget that you're being
monitored at all times.
We're talking about one
measly esper kid, right?
We've got six. This'll be easy.
That's just based on eyewitness accounts.
Yeah, whatever.
You newbies are gonna have to listen to us.
Just so you know, we get all the loot--
I'll go by myself.
The target can't be taken lightly.
--You bastard! --What the hell'd you do?!
--Kill! Kill! Kill!
Is the target someone you know?
I can feel his power...
...growing even stronger.
Aw, jeez.
We should hurry. Open the back.
Be careful out there, Boss.
Hatori.
Hey, where's your parachute?
There was a blue light shining
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM
What remained even after I swiped
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me
Yes, I want someone to understand...
This wish that's hidden colorless and invisible
The breath I was holding deep within my heart
I let it all out at once and return to my senses
On days that I'm feeling apathetic
it suddenly comes to mind
These seasons I spent as if they were a given
Even if reality becomes sullied
Only the sky we saw together is real
This is more incomprehensible
Than the grammar on the blackboard
If it's going to disappear within 24 hours
This flowing story is just too lonely
I just can't do it
Just like that back hip circle I gave up on
But I'm not going to...
Give up
My present anymore
I adorn my overflowing emotions
And run through my worries and hesitations
It can't be decided from 0 to 100
Draw the incomplete future with this hand
We can't even prove its existence
But as the world stabs the middle of my chest
It overflows with cobalt blue
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor:
Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan
Nii-san, I haven't seen you
in that state for a while.
I'd always been afraid that this thing
would emerge from you again.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 11:
"Mob 3
- Trauma."
"Mob 3 - Trauma-~"
"Mob 3 - Trauma-~.
"Mob 3
~Trauma~"